import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Из статей по апдейтам ангуляра',
  cards: [
    {
      "question": "to graduate",
      "answer": "оканчивать школу/универ/курсы (обучение)"
    },
    {
      "question": "from here on",
      "answer": "с этого момента и далее"
    },
    {
      "question": "gradually",
      "answer": "постепенно"
    },
    {
      "question": "inheritance",
      "answer": "наследство"
    },
    {
      "question": "trait",
      "answer": "черта"
    },
    {
      "question": "with the difference that",
      "answer": "с той разницей, что"
    },
    {
      "question": "survey",
      "answer": "опрос"
    },
    {
      "question": "struggles",
      "answer": "трудности"
    },
    {
      "question": "to face",
      "answer": "сталкиваться"
    },
    {
      "question": "to suffer",
      "answer": "страдать"
    },
    {
      "question": "significant",
      "answer": "значительный"
    },
    {
      "question": "milestone",
      "answer": "важный этап"
    },
    {
      "question": "simplicity",
      "answer": "простота"
    },
    {
      "question": "dozen",
      "answer": "дюжина"
    },
    {
      "question": "entirely",
      "answer": "полностью"
    },
    {
      "question": "above",
      "answer": "над/ранее/выше"
    },
    {
      "question": "interoperability",
      "answer": "совместимость"
    },
    {
      "question": "to avoid",
      "answer": "избегать"
    },
    {
      "question": "stepping stone",
      "answer": "ступенька"
    },
    {
      "question": "to emphasize",
      "answer": "подчеркивать"
    },
    {
      "question": "numerous",
      "answer": "многочисленный"
    }
  ]

} as Category;
